I'm not even going to front y'all.
Like, I watch these videos of brilliant autistic people.
And I know there's people who are like, Amanda Seals, she self-diagnosed is autistic.
And I'm going to just keep it a buck with y'all.
I'm good at so much that there was no question that I'm autistic.
You can't be good at drawing, good at singing, good at writing, good at speaking, good at painting, good.
Like, you can't, you can't be good at that many things.
Good at DJing, good at graphic arts.
You can't be good at that many things.
Good at acting, good at playing piano.
You can't be good at that many things and not be autistic.
I'm around you.
If there was any proof that I was autistic, it was that I got mad talents, B.
And I speak loud.
Support a real one.